- [Manny] Have you mastered React
or wondered how to build a backend with React?
Would you like to learn more about Node, Express, and Mongo,
and how they integrate with React
as a full-stack application?
If the answer is yes to any of these questions,
you've come to the right place.
We'll set up the required libraries and tools to get going.
Next, we'll set the stage for a backend
with our initial Node and Express server.
Then we'll set up our Mongo database
along with defining all the routing endpoints.
And finally, we'll create a React frontend and add a form
and the UI elements to present our data to our users.
Hi, I'm Manny Henry, and I've been working with Node,
React, and JavaScript for a very long time.
So if you're ready to build
your own full-stack application with MERN,
fire up your favorite editor and let's get started.